<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-11-26T15:53:13+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/</id><title type="html">PGA Reach</title><subtitle>Impacting lives through golf.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Metropolitan PGA Section &amp;amp; PGA HOPE</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/metropolitan-pga-section-pga-hope-3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Metropolitan PGA Section &amp; PGA HOPE" /><published>2016-07-12T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-07-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/metropolitan-pga-section-pga-hope-3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/metropolitan-pga-section-pga-hope-3.html">&lt;p&gt;PALM BEACH GARDENS, Fla. (May23, 2017)PGA REACH, the 501 (c)(3) charitable foundation of the PGA of America—in conjunction with the Middle Atlantic PGA Section Foundation—has selectedTajma Brown, a 2016 Hampton University graduate,for the PGA WORKS Internship program. PGA WORKSaspires to be the most valuableinternship opportunity for individuals from diverse backgrounds to garner experience in all facets of the golf industry.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The PGA of America recognizes that it will be defined by how its commitment to diversity and inclusion resonates throughout its programs and practices. This commitment is vital to the health and relevance of the Association’s business and the game overall.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;“All career paths start with awareness and opportunity, and providing individuals from diverse backgrounds entry into the golf industryis a priority for PGA REACH,” said Ryan Cannon, Senior Director, PGA REACH. “PGA WORKS is an importantinitiative, and we’re thrilled to have Tajmabegin her career in golf with the Middle Atlantic PGA Foundation.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Brownearned her Masters Degree in Sports Management from West Virginia University. Shewill support programming of the Middle Atlantic PGA Foundation,which serves as the philanthropic entity of the Section.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A resident of Wilmington, Delaware, Brown’s experience includes serving as an internfor the NBA’s Philadelphia 76ers andMinor League Baseball’sWilmington Blue Rocks.She worked in several capacities for Hampton University’sDepartment of Athleticsand foundedthe school’s Sport Management Club.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;“In five years, I see myself working with a task force at the PGA to help bring more womenand other minority groups into the game,” said Brown. “I believe that to tackle the issue of diversity and inclusion in golf, it must start with the marketing and promotion of programs that already exist, specifically speaking on programs for youth.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;For more information on PGA REACH, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://pgareach.org/pga&quot;&gt;www.pgareach.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://pgareach.org/metropolitan-pga-section-pga-hope-3/undefined&quot;&gt;. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;ABOUT PGA REACH&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;PGA REACH is the charitable foundation of the PGA of America. By aligning with the 41 PGA Sections and charitable partners throughout the United States, PGA REACH positively impacts lives through golf. The programming created and supported by PGA REACH focuses on serving three key pillars:Youth, Military and Diversity &amp;amp;Inclusion.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;CONTACT&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Michael Abramowitz PGA of America 561/624-8458 mabramowitz@pgahq.com&lt;br /&gt;
        Ethan Brady Middle Atlantic PGA Section 540/784-4648 ebrady@pgahq.com&lt;br /&gt;
        Jared MinskiMastro Communications 732/469-5700jared@mastrocomm.com&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">PALM BEACH GARDENS, Fla. (May23, 2017)PGA REACH, the 501 (c)(3) charitable foundation of the PGA of America—in conjunction with the Middle Atlantic PGA Section Foundation—has selectedTajma Brown, a 2016 Hampton University graduate,for the PGA WORKS Internship program. PGA WORKSaspires to be the most valuableinternship opportunity for individuals from diverse backgrounds to garner experience in all facets of the golf industry. The PGA of America recognizes that it will be defined by how its commitment to diversity and inclusion resonates throughout its programs and practices. This commitment is vital to the health and relevance of the Association’s business and the game overall. “All career paths start with awareness and opportunity, and providing individuals from diverse backgrounds entry into the golf industryis a priority for PGA REACH,” said Ryan Cannon, Senior Director, PGA REACH. “PGA WORKS is an importantinitiative, and we’re thrilled to have Tajmabegin her career in golf with the Middle Atlantic PGA Foundation.” Brownearned her Masters Degree in Sports Management from West Virginia University. Shewill support programming of the Middle Atlantic PGA Foundation,which serves as the philanthropic entity of the Section. A resident of Wilmington, Delaware, Brown’s experience includes serving as an internfor the NBA’s Philadelphia 76ers andMinor League Baseball’sWilmington Blue Rocks.She worked in several capacities for Hampton University’sDepartment of Athleticsand foundedthe school’s Sport Management Club. “In five years, I see myself working with a task force at the PGA to help bring more womenand other minority groups into the game,” said Brown. “I believe that to tackle the issue of diversity and inclusion in golf, it must start with the marketing and promotion of programs that already exist, specifically speaking on programs for youth.” For more information on PGA REACH, visit www.pgareach.org. ABOUT PGA REACH PGA REACH is the charitable foundation of the PGA of America. By aligning with the 41 PGA Sections and charitable partners throughout the United States, PGA REACH positively impacts lives through golf. The programming created and supported by PGA REACH focuses on serving three key pillars:Youth, Military and Diversity &amp;amp;Inclusion. CONTACT Michael Abramowitz PGA of America 561/624-8458 mabramowitz@pgahq.com Ethan Brady Middle Atlantic PGA Section 540/784-4648 ebrady@pgahq.com Jared MinskiMastro Communications 732/469-5700jared@mastrocomm.com</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">PGA of America Donates $100,000 to Benton Harbor Promise</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/pga-of-america-donates-100000-to-benton-harbor-promise.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PGA of America Donates $100,000 to Benton Harbor Promise" /><published>2016-05-27T10:21:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-05-27T10:21:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/pga-of-america-donates-100000-to-benton-harbor-promise</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/pga-of-america-donates-100000-to-benton-harbor-promise.html">&lt;p&gt;Today, at the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.srpga.com&quot;&gt;77th Senior PGA Championship presented by KitchenAid&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pga.com/pga-america&quot;&gt;PGA of America&lt;/a&gt;, through its charitable foundation PGA REACH, announced a donation of $100,000 to Benton Harbor Promise, a scholarship program that provides free two-year tuition to a community college or career technical program in Michigan for qualifying Benton Harbor students. The donation was made possible from funds raised through the National Car Rental/Michigan PGA Section Pro-Am and the Senior PGA Championship Pro-Am, both of which were played earlier this week at Point O’ Woods Country Club and Harbor Shores, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The $100,000 donation was presented to Benton Harbor Promise Chairwomen, Cathy Averill and Dr. Lynn Todman during the Host Community Breakfast, featuring government representatives from the state, at Harbor Shores in Benton Harbor, Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;“We are thrilled and so thankful for the continued support that we receive from PGA REACH each year and its dedication to improving the lives of our young community members,” said Dr. Todman, chairman of Benton Harbor Promise. “This generous donation will help pave the path for future generations in Benton Harbor and continue to inspire young people in our area for years to come.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Benton Harbor Promise launched its scholarship program in 2011, two years after legislation was signed by then Governor Jennifer Granholm awarding ten Promise Zone designations in communities across Michigan, including Benton Harbor. This year’s graduating class is the sixth class of scholarship eligible students for Benton Harbor Promise.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;“Together, with National Car Rental, we are thrilled to invest in the Benton Harbor community, building opportunities and enriching the lives of future generations and residents of this area,” said Scott Kmiec, senior director of PGA REACH. “This donation to Benton Harbor Promise will help provide opportunities for the students of this community for years to come. We look forward to watching the positive impact unfold.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Senior PGA Championship presented by KitchenAid, the most historic and prestigious senior major, features the strongest field in senior golf. Players in this year’s field include 2014 and 2015 Champion Colin Montgomerie, 2012 Champion Roger Chapman and John Daly. For more information about the 77th Senior PGA Championship, or to buy tickets, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.srpga.com&quot;&gt;SrPGA.com&lt;/a&gt; or call 1-800-PGA-GOLF (800-742-4653).&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;For more information about KitchenAid, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kitchenaid.com/&quot;&gt;KitchenAid.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/KitchenAid?_rdr&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/KitchenAid_Golf&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;. For more information about the PGA of America, visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pga.org/&quot;&gt;PGA.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today, at the 77th Senior PGA Championship presented by KitchenAid, the PGA of America, through its charitable foundation PGA REACH, announced a donation of $100,000 to Benton Harbor Promise, a scholarship program that provides free two-year tuition to a community college or career technical program in Michigan for qualifying Benton Harbor students. The donation was made possible from funds raised through the National Car Rental/Michigan PGA Section Pro-Am and the Senior PGA Championship Pro-Am, both of which were played earlier this week at Point O’ Woods Country Club and Harbor Shores, respectively. The $100,000 donation was presented to Benton Harbor Promise Chairwomen, Cathy Averill and Dr. Lynn Todman during the Host Community Breakfast, featuring government representatives from the state, at Harbor Shores in Benton Harbor, Michigan. “We are thrilled and so thankful for the continued support that we receive from PGA REACH each year and its dedication to improving the lives of our young community members,” said Dr. Todman, chairman of Benton Harbor Promise. “This generous donation will help pave the path for future generations in Benton Harbor and continue to inspire young people in our area for years to come.” Benton Harbor Promise launched its scholarship program in 2011, two years after legislation was signed by then Governor Jennifer Granholm awarding ten Promise Zone designations in communities across Michigan, including Benton Harbor. This year’s graduating class is the sixth class of scholarship eligible students for Benton Harbor Promise. “Together, with National Car Rental, we are thrilled to invest in the Benton Harbor community, building opportunities and enriching the lives of future generations and residents of this area,” said Scott Kmiec, senior director of PGA REACH. “This donation to Benton Harbor Promise will help provide opportunities for the students of this community for years to come. We look forward to watching the positive impact unfold.” The Senior PGA Championship presented by KitchenAid, the most historic and prestigious senior major, features the strongest field in senior golf. Players in this year’s field include 2014 and 2015 Champion Colin Montgomerie, 2012 Champion Roger Chapman and John Daly. For more information about the 77th Senior PGA Championship, or to buy tickets, visit SrPGA.com or call 1-800-PGA-GOLF (800-742-4653). For more information about KitchenAid, visit KitchenAid.com, Facebook, or Twitter. For more information about the PGA of America, visit PGA.org.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Marriott Golf Announces Hit The Green For Hope Memorial Day Weekend Promotion In Support Of Pga Reach Military Veterans Nationwide</title><link href="http://0.0.0.0:4000/marriott-golf-announces-hit-the-green-for-hope-memorial-day-weekend-promotion-in-support-of-pga-reach-military-veterans-nationwide.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marriott Golf Announces Hit The Green For Hope Memorial Day Weekend Promotion In Support Of Pga Reach Military Veterans Nationwide" /><published>2016-05-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-05-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://0.0.0.0:4000/marriott-golf-announces-hit-the-green-for-hope-memorial-day-weekend-promotion-in-support-of-pga-reach-military-veterans-nationwide</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://0.0.0.0:4000/marriott-golf-announces-hit-the-green-for-hope-memorial-day-weekend-promotion-in-support-of-pga-reach-military-veterans-nationwide.html">&lt;p&gt;Marriott Golf, one of the world’s premier golf operators, has teamed up with PGA REACH – the charitable foundation of the PGA of America – to launch &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hit the Green for HOPE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a Memorial Day Weekend campaign in support of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;PGA HOPE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; – golf programming for United States military Veterans with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Golfers will have the opportunity to take part in the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hit the Green for HOPE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; promotion at 17 participating Marriott Golf properties nationwide. By donating $10, on a designated par-3 hole at each property, any golfer that hits the green on his/her tee shot receives a certificate valid for 30% off “their next purchase” in the golf shop. All participating golfers who do not hit the green will receive a certificate valid for 15% off “their next purchase” in the golf shop. The certificates are valid for merchandise only, and all certificates are valid through Dec. 31, 2016, at the golf shop of the participating property.  100% of proceeds from the campaign will be used to support and enhance **PGA HOPE **programming.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PGA HOPE **&lt;em&gt;(Helping Our Patriots Everywhere)&lt;/em&gt; is the flagship Military program of PGA REACH – the charitable foundation of the PGA of America. The HOPE program introduces golf to Veterans with disabilities in order to enhance their physical, mental, social and emotional well-being. Led by PGA Professionals, **PGA HOPE&lt;/strong&gt; is a proven activity that has helped thousands of Veterans assimilate back into their communities through the social interaction the game of golf provides. All &lt;strong&gt;PGA HOPE **programming is fully funded by PGA REACH and offered at **_NO COST _&lt;/strong&gt;for military Veterans.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;“Military Veterans have made tremendous sacrifices to protect our freedom, and it’s important that we all do our part, as many struggle with the transition back to civilian life,” said Bill Nault, Vice President, Marriott Golf. “&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;PGA HOPE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is a fantastic program that inspires wounded Veterans to learn and play golf as a therapeutic form of their rehabilitation, and it’s rewarding to see Marriott Golf take such an active role in supporting a program that is truly making a difference for thousands of Veterans.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Participants of &lt;strong&gt;HOPE **programs include military Veterans living with physical or cognitive challenges such as Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI), Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) and amputees, among other challenges.  As golf has become a therapeutic part of the rehabilitation process for many Veterans with disabilities, it is only fitting that Veterans who have participated in **HOPE&lt;/strong&gt; programming will be on-site at several participating locations during the Memorial Day Weekend promotional period.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;“We are very excited to align PGA REACH and our flagship military program &lt;strong&gt;PGA HOPE&lt;/strong&gt; with Marriott Golf and its portfolio of resort and championship golf venues,” said Scott Kmiec, Senior Director of PGA REACH. “Through programming like &lt;strong&gt;PGA HOPE&lt;/strong&gt;, and thanks to the corporate responsibility of organizations like Marriott Golf, the PGA of America will be in a position to make a more meaningful impact on the lives of America’s military Veterans.”&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Participating courses in the &lt;strong&gt;_Hit the Green for HOPE _&lt;/strong&gt;campaign represent some of the country’s premier championship venues, including: Wildfire Golf Club, Phoenix, Ariz.; Camelback Golf Club, Scottsdale, Ariz.; Starr Pass Country Club, Tucson, Ariz.; Desert Springs Golf Resort, Palm Desert, Calif.; Shadow Ridge Golf Club, Palm Desert, Calif.; Grande Vista Golf Club, Orlando, Fla.; Hawk’s Landing Golf Club, Orlando, Fla.; Ritz-Carlton Golf Club, Grande Lakes, Orlando, Fla.; The Rookery &amp;amp; Hammock Bay, Marco Island, Fla.;  Renaissance Vinoy Golf Club,  St. Petersburg, Fla.; Ritz-Carlton Members Club, Sarasota, Fla.; Stone Mountain Golf Club, Stone Mountain, Ga.; Griffin Gate Golf Club, Lexington, Ky.; Toftrees Golf Club, State College, Pa.; Gaylord Springs Golf Club, Nashville, Tenn.; Cattails Golf Club, Kingsport, Tenn.; and Westfields Golf Club, Clifton, Va.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;For more information on the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hit the Green for HOPE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; campaign and additional military programming at Marriott Golf facilities, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.MarriottGolf.com&quot;&gt;www.MarriottGolf.com&lt;/a&gt;.**  &lt;strong&gt;For more information on **&lt;em&gt;PGA HOPE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, please visit &lt;a href=&quot;https://pgareach.com&quot;&gt;www.pgareach.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;** **&lt;em&gt;About Marriott Golf&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Marriott Golf manages 50 golf courses in 12 countries across four continents, offering nearly 1,000 holes of championship golf for Marriott International brands, including The Ritz-Carlton, JW Marriott, Marriott Hotels and Resorts, Gaylord Hotels, Renaissance Hotels, and Marriott Golf Academy.  Marriott has managed golf operations since 1971 and is one of the world’s premier golf operators.  Marriott provides golf development expertise, golf management, and consulting services to a unique variety of hospitality environments including resorts, private membership clubs, daily fee courses, golf schools, and franchises. For more information, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://golf.marriott-vacations.com/leisure/default.jsp&quot;&gt;www.marriottgolf.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Click here for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.marriott.com/corporateinfo/boilerplate.mi&quot;&gt;Marriott International, Inc. (NYSE:MAR)&lt;/a&gt; company information.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;About PGA REACH&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;PGA REACH serves as the charitable foundation of the PGA of America. Through the game of golf, PGA REACH fosters inclusion and positively impacts youth, military veterans and diverse communities. Aligned with the PGA of America’s 41 Section offices and charitable partners, PGA REACH leverages the game of golf to make a difference in the communities we serve.  For more information please visit [&lt;em&gt;www.pgareach.com.]&lt;a href=&quot;https://pgareach.com&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Marriott Golf, one of the world’s premier golf operators, has teamed up with PGA REACH – the charitable foundation of the PGA of America – to launch Hit the Green for HOPE, a Memorial Day Weekend campaign in support of PGA HOPE – golf programming for United States military Veterans with disabilities. Golfers will have the opportunity to take part in the Hit the Green for HOPE promotion at 17 participating Marriott Golf properties nationwide. By donating $10, on a designated par-3 hole at each property, any golfer that hits the green on his/her tee shot receives a certificate valid for 30% off “their next purchase” in the golf shop. All participating golfers who do not hit the green will receive a certificate valid for 15% off “their next purchase” in the golf shop. The certificates are valid for merchandise only, and all certificates are valid through Dec. 31, 2016, at the golf shop of the participating property. 100% of proceeds from the campaign will be used to support and enhance **PGA HOPE **programming. PGA HOPE **(Helping Our Patriots Everywhere) is the flagship Military program of PGA REACH – the charitable foundation of the PGA of America. The HOPE program introduces golf to Veterans with disabilities in order to enhance their physical, mental, social and emotional well-being. Led by PGA Professionals, **PGA HOPE is a proven activity that has helped thousands of Veterans assimilate back into their communities through the social interaction the game of golf provides. All PGA HOPE **programming is fully funded by PGA REACH and offered at **_NO COST _for military Veterans. “Military Veterans have made tremendous sacrifices to protect our freedom, and it’s important that we all do our part, as many struggle with the transition back to civilian life,” said Bill Nault, Vice President, Marriott Golf. “PGA HOPE is a fantastic program that inspires wounded Veterans to learn and play golf as a therapeutic form of their rehabilitation, and it’s rewarding to see Marriott Golf take such an active role in supporting a program that is truly making a difference for thousands of Veterans.” Participants of HOPE **programs include military Veterans living with physical or cognitive challenges such as Traumatic Brain Injury (TBI), Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder (PTSD) and amputees, among other challenges. As golf has become a therapeutic part of the rehabilitation process for many Veterans with disabilities, it is only fitting that Veterans who have participated in **HOPE programming will be on-site at several participating locations during the Memorial Day Weekend promotional period. “We are very excited to align PGA REACH and our flagship military program PGA HOPE with Marriott Golf and its portfolio of resort and championship golf venues,” said Scott Kmiec, Senior Director of PGA REACH. “Through programming like PGA HOPE, and thanks to the corporate responsibility of organizations like Marriott Golf, the PGA of America will be in a position to make a more meaningful impact on the lives of America’s military Veterans.” Participating courses in the _Hit the Green for HOPE _campaign represent some of the country’s premier championship venues, including: Wildfire Golf Club, Phoenix, Ariz.; Camelback Golf Club, Scottsdale, Ariz.; Starr Pass Country Club, Tucson, Ariz.; Desert Springs Golf Resort, Palm Desert, Calif.; Shadow Ridge Golf Club, Palm Desert, Calif.; Grande Vista Golf Club, Orlando, Fla.; Hawk’s Landing Golf Club, Orlando, Fla.; Ritz-Carlton Golf Club, Grande Lakes, Orlando, Fla.; The Rookery &amp;amp; Hammock Bay, Marco Island, Fla.; Renaissance Vinoy Golf Club, St. Petersburg, Fla.; Ritz-Carlton Members Club, Sarasota, Fla.; Stone Mountain Golf Club, Stone Mountain, Ga.; Griffin Gate Golf Club, Lexington, Ky.; Toftrees Golf Club, State College, Pa.; Gaylord Springs Golf Club, Nashville, Tenn.; Cattails Golf Club, Kingsport, Tenn.; and Westfields Golf Club, Clifton, Va. For more information on the Hit the Green for HOPE campaign and additional military programming at Marriott Golf facilities, please visit www.MarriottGolf.com.** For more information on **PGA HOPE, please visit www.pgareach.com. ** **About Marriott Golf Marriott Golf manages 50 golf courses in 12 countries across four continents, offering nearly 1,000 holes of championship golf for Marriott International brands, including The Ritz-Carlton, JW Marriott, Marriott Hotels and Resorts, Gaylord Hotels, Renaissance Hotels, and Marriott Golf Academy. Marriott has managed golf operations since 1971 and is one of the world’s premier golf operators. Marriott provides golf development expertise, golf management, and consulting services to a unique variety of hospitality environments including resorts, private membership clubs, daily fee courses, golf schools, and franchises. For more information, visit www.marriottgolf.com. Click here for Marriott International, Inc. (NYSE:MAR) company information. About PGA REACH PGA REACH serves as the charitable foundation of the PGA of America. Through the game of golf, PGA REACH fosters inclusion and positively impacts youth, military veterans and diverse communities. Aligned with the PGA of America’s 41 Section offices and charitable partners, PGA REACH leverages the game of golf to make a difference in the communities we serve. For more information please visit [www.pgareach.com.]2</summary></entry></feed>